=== E-Commerce by SalesCart ===
Contributors: SalesCart
Tags: salescart, shopping cart,ecommerce,wordpress ecommerce,wp e-commerce,paypal,payments,credit card,e-commerce,online store,store,shop,cart,online shop,shopping,digital goods,downloadable products,product catalog,ecomerce,products,facebook,f-commerce,pinterest,p-commerce
Tested up to: 4.1
Requires at least: 2.8
Stable tag: trunk
License: GPLv2, URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

SalesCart is a Full featured Shopping Cart/E-commerce solution that can be added in under 15 mins. to any WP theme. Use SalesCart for FREE today.

== Description ==
SalesCart is a 100% complete shopping cart from the originators of plug-in E-commerce. It is so EASY - ANYONE can do it! SalesCart will work with any theme, any website, any hosting.  Best of all, it will be easier, less expensive, more complete, and more secure than any other shopping cart plug-in.  Its also 100% free up to 10 products and more economical than many other solutions with built-in credit card processing at reasonable rates as low as 1.89%.  You can also get a card swiper plug-in for your mobile device that will allow you to take retail face-to-face sales.

= 100% Security =
Why is SalesCart so secure?  It is the first (1st) shopping cart on the planet that is out-of-scope for PCI because credit card data is "always" entered by your customer directly into your banks payment gateway bypassing your website, your blog, and your web hosting.  This greatly simplifies your stores compliance with PCI and eliminates monthly PCI fees.  Secure and encrypted http protocol is included and guarantees all extra customer communications.  

= FREE Commerce =
SalesCart provides a *forever* free version.  No credit card required to try or test out SalesCart, and if you have less than 10 products, you can just use the free version.

= Accept Payments =
You don't have to get a separate merchant account and try and figure out how to integrate it with SalesCart.  SalesCart comes complete with payment acceptance and a REAL merchant account.  You will be able to accept credit cards at b-to-b rates lower than 2%.  In addition, get a card swipe plug-in for your mobile phone or tablet and take retail sales that integrate as well with your same online store.

= Full-featured Shopping Cart =
SalesCart has features like toggle between a single-page checkout or a step-wise checkout system - your choice.  In addition, all editions come with advanced features like real-time shipping and abandoned cart reporting.  Automatic and customized SEO is also included free.  

= Social/Mobile/Cloning Commerce =
A SalesCart store displays anywhere and everywhere.  At the end of installation, in addition to your WordPress web store, you will have a free Facebook store, a free mobile store, and you can instantly push your store products to Pinterest, Twitter, or anywhere else.  In fact, you are not even limited to one web store, you can literally clone your store and create thousands of distribution points and that means more sales for you.  Your products are all automatically synchronized across all store display points.

= Instant Upgrades =
Upgrades to the software are instantly pushed and merged into your store.  You don't have to re-integrate or merge your theme to make everything work again. 

== Installation ==
= Automatic Installation =
1. Visit your WordPress Site or blog, and **click** on *{Dashboard}*
1. In the WordPress dashboard, **click** on *{Plugins}*, and **select** → *{Add New}*
1. In the Search Plugins box, **type** `salescart` and **press** the *{Enter key}* on your keyboard
1. In the Search results, find the `E-commerce by SalesCart` plugin and **click** *{Install now}* to install it
1. After the plugin is installed **click** *{Activate Plugin}*
1. **Navigate** to *{SalesCart Store}* in the Wordpress dashboard admin and follow the instructions provided on the screen 

= Manual Installation =
1. On this page, **click** on the *{Download}* button
1. **Save** the `zip file` to any place on your device that you can find later
1. In the WordPress dashboard, **click** on *{Plugins}*, and **select**→ *{Add New}*
1. **Click** the *{Upload}* link, **choose** the saved zip file from the location you saved it to previously 
1. After the plugin is installed **click** *{Activate Plugin}*
1. **Navigate** to *{SalesCart Store}* in the Wordpress dashboard admin and follow the instructions provided

= Alternative Advanced Server Installation =
1. This assumes you have direct control and access to the server.
1. **Transfer** the downloaded *zip file* to the server and **extract** the contents into the `wp-content/plugins/` directory for your particular WordPress website installation
1. Then, **activate** the plugin via the WordPress Dashboard

== Screenshots ==

1. WordPress Store
2. Product Detail
3. Single Page Checkout
4. Mobile store 
5. Facebook Store
6. Pinterest Store

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

* [FAQ / Knowledgebase] (http://support.salescart.com/kb/start-search.asp)
* [Help Center] (http://forum.salescart.com)

== Changelog ==

= 1.0.0 =
* First Release

== Upgrade Notice ==
None